Arlene Blum papers, M1558
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 4: Slides (from accession 2010-021)
  - Places, events, and people; arranged chronologically.
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 9-11) (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 12-14) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 15-17) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 18-21) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 22-25) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 26-28) (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 29,30,35) (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 36,40,41) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987: Unnumbered rolls (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Champex, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Undated/Unlabeled (Box 42, Folder 10)